purplista.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Purplista

Purplista does everything in its capacity to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Your Personal Information and to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access, alteration or disclosure or destruction. Purplista is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive Your Personal Information. The Website is also linked to many other sites and we are not/shall be not responsible for their privacy policies or practices as it is beyond our control. Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, Purplista cannot be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event (as defined below). A "Force Majeure Event" shall mean any event that is beyond the reasonable control of Purplista and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorized access to computer data and storage device, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption, etc.

### 1\. Our Commitment

We respect your Privacy and this document presents the Privacy Policy followed by the website www.purplista.com. This policy forms part of the detailed terms under which a user can use the services of the website and may be modified by us from time to time which you are required to verify periodically.

### 2\. Consent

Your use of the website is deemed as a consent for the policies mentioned here in under which your personal information is collected and processed by us.

### 3\. Information Collected

  * When any user visits the website www.purplista.com certain technical information about the user is identified and in some cases recorded by us in order to assist in the administration and for the enhancement of the user experience. Such information includes. 

 i. The Browser used by the user

ii. The different pages visited by the user on the website

  * When you register as a member of the services offered by the website: 

 i. Personal information provided for registration such as Name, Address, Phone number, E Mail address etc.

ii. Any other information that may be required to be collected under the prevailing law in force in India.

  * When you send enquiries to buy goods and services on the website 

 i. Information about who the product you are interested in.

ii. It is also understood that any communication sent by you to Purplista for enquiry/ grievance may be recorded by the company in specifically designated folders

### 4\. Cookies

We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. However we do not store any personally identifiable information in cookies. The session cookie expires when you close your browser.

### 5\. How the Information is used ?

 i. Any information collected by the website is shared within the Company on a need to know basis.

ii. Information collected may be shared with law enforcement agencies as per the provisions of law prevailing in India.

### 6\. How the Information is Secured ?

  * The Company adopts reasonable security practices to ensure security of the personal information collected from the user and to prevent unauthorized access, modification or deletion.
  * We have taken reasonable precautions to prevent any malicious codes on the website. However users are requested to use discretion before clicking on any hyper link on the website and ensure that they donot represent any disguised misdirection or lead to any malicious sites.
  * Sensitive personal information collected from the users such as the Password of the user is stored in suitable encrypted/hashed form.
  * The company will periodically assess the risks around user registration and passwords and based on the risks increase the security measures and practices, especially around account lock outs, passwords, and additional authentication mechanisms

###  7\. Transfer of Information

The personal information collected from the users is not transferred to any agency unless such agency is also contractually bound to follow adequate security standards as required under Indian law.

### 8\. Retention of Information

Personal information collected from the users is retained in a secure manner for a reasonable period as long as the information is required to be retained as per the requirements under Indian law.We do not sell your email id or any identifiable information to any third party, however we may use this information to derive insights on consumer preference and buying patterns. Purplista reserves the right to use these insights in anyway possible without divulging identifiable information of an individual.

### 9\. External Links

This privacy policy is limited to the information collected us while the user uses the website. The website may however contain links to other websites. Such sites may have their own privacy policies and users are required to peruse and take note of such policies.

### 10\. Grievance Redressal

Following is the grievance redressal officer who will receive complaints if any and redress the grievance of users as per a structured grievance redressal policy adopted by the website  
Name:  
E Mail: 

### 11\. Discriminatory policy

While website collects information which may identify the user on gender or ethnic basis, Website does in no way discriminate the user based on gender, color, creed or ethnicity. All our services are completely impartial in these terms.
